{
    "subject": "resource/Lilian_Velez",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Philippines",
    "human_readable": "Lilian Velez was born in the Philippines.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9379894733428955,
            "question": "Is Lilian Velez originally from the Philippines?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9036383628845215,
            "question": "Lilian Velez was born in which location?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8721938729286194,
            "question": "Where was Lilian Velez born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6517648100852966,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Lilian Velez?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5881710052490234,
            "question": "What country is Lilian Velez from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5583368539810181,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Lilian Velez's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4608418345451355,
            "question": "What is the name of Lilian Velez's country of origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39472442865371704,
            "question": "Is the Philippines a known place for birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.303201824426651,
            "question": "Where did Lilian Velez spend her early years?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11731502413749695,
            "question": "What are some cultural aspects associated with the Philippines?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Lilian Velez was born in the Philippines.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5431_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Lilian Velez spend her early years?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5431_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is the Philippines a known place for birth?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5431_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Lilian Velez's country of origin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5431_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5431_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5431_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5431_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5431_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5431_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5431_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5431_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5431_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5431_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5431_70.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple instances confirming that Lilian Velez was born in Cebu City, Philippines, such as in `40.txt`, `70.txt`, and `61.txt`. Therefore, the statement \"Lilian Velez was born in the Philippines\" is supported by the provided information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}